Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series IV: Subject Files, 13180
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists, 13218
    - Kaz, undated; 13288 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack, undated; 13287 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Kerouac, Jan, undated; 13286 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Kolm, Ron, undated; 13285 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated; 13284 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Kruger, Barbara, undated; 13283 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Kupferberg, Tuli, undated; 13281 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - LaPrade, Erik, undated; 13280 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - LaTour, Jose, undated; 13279 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Lewis, Marilyn Jane, undated; 13278 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Lifshin, Lyn, undated; 13277 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Linquist, Ona, undated; 13276 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Litzky, Tsaurah, undated; 13275 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Lupino, Stephan, undated; 13274 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Mandl, David, undated; 13273 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Manister, Diana, undated; 13272 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Martin, Douglas, undated; 13271 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Maynard, Joe, undated; 13270 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - McGonigle, Thomas, undated; 13269 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Mesmer, Sharon, undated; 13268 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Minkowitz, Donna, undated; 13267 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Mueller, Cookie, undated; 13266 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Nersesian, Arthur, undated; 13265 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Nostrand, Jennifer, undated; 13264 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Nufer, Doug, undated; 13263 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Nurske, Dennis, undated; 13262 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - O'Brien, Geoffrey, undated; 13261 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Ostashevsky, Eugene, undated; 13260 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Padua, Jose, undated; 13259 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Passaro, Vince, undated; 13258 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Peabody, Richard, undated; 13257 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Piazza, Tom, undated; 13256 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Plantenga, Bart, undated; 13255 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Polonoff, David, undated; 13253 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Reith, Gerry, undated; 13252 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Rose, Joel, undated; 13251 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Rutkowski, Thaddeus, undated; 13250 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Sand, Catherine Rutgers, undated; 13249 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Sandlin, David, undated; 13248 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Savage, Tom, undated; 13245 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Saxon, Erik, undated; 13244 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Schneeman, Carolee, undated; 13243 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Siegle, Robert, undated; 13242 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Sirowitz, Hal, undated; 13241 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Sparrow, undated; 13240 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Speigelman, Art, undated; 13238 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Strausbaugh, John, undated; 13237 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Sukenick, Ronald, undated; 13236 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Tillman, Lynne, undated; 13235 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Tobocman, Seth, undated; 13234 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Topp, Mike, undated; 13233 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Torres, Edwin, undated; 13232 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Ulin, David, undated; 13231 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Watson, Carl, undated; 13229 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Weber, Bruce, undated; 13228 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated; 13227 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Winter, Patricia, undated; 13226 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Wittig, Rob, undated; 13225 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated; 13223 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Wood, Arthur, undated; 13221 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Wortsman, Peter, undated; 13220 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Author Misc., undated; 13219 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects, 13181
    - Appearances Magazine, undated; 13217 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Between C & D, undated; 13216 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Big Cigars Magazine, undated; 13214 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Bindlestiff Family Cirkus, undated; 13213 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Coney Island, USA, undated; 13212 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Digitas, undated; 13211 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Downtown writers and artists, undated; 13210 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - East Village scene, undated; 13209 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Eastern News Distributors, undated; 13208 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Evening of Romance, undated; 13207 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - The Fugs, undated; 13206 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Heretical Society, undated; 13205 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Low Tech Manual, undated; 13204 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Magazines, undated; 13203 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - New Observations, undated; 13202 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Outlaw Bible, undated; 13201 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Outlaw Poets' Reading, Oct. 22, 1999, 13200 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - PIM, undated; 13199 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Paper Tiger TV, undated; 13198 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Phun Phactory, undated; 13197 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Pink Pages, undated; 13196 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Poetry, undated; 13195 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - PopSmear Magazine, undated; 13194 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Public Illumination Magazine, undated; 13193 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Rank Cologne, undated; 13192 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Rant, undated; 13191 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Raw, undated; 13190 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Readings, undated; 13189 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - St. Mark's Bookshop, undated; 13188 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - Soft Skull Press, undated; 13187 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Snake Eyes 2, undated; 13185 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - WFMU, undated; 13184 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - General Subject Misc., undated; 13183 (Box 18, Folder 105)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series V: Photographs, 13171
  - Unbearables, by Lydia Tomkin, undated; 13179 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Kolm, Mesmer and Ackerman, undated; 13178 (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Mary Leary, undated; 13177 (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Philly Reading 1998, by Bonny Finberg, 13176 (Box 18, Folder 109)
  - Unbearables at Halloween party, by C. Wierzbicki, undated; 13175 (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Unbearables at Magazine Put-together party, by L. Tomkin, undated; 13174 (Box 18, Folder 111)
  - Unbearables' Atlantic City trip, 7/24/99, 1999; 13173 (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - Unbearable Banquet at 'Ukranian National Home,' by Lydia Tomkin (10/22/99), 1999; 13172 (Box 18, Folder 113)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series VI: Announcements, 13011
  - Subseries A: Readings, 13063
    - 76 Varick, undated; 13170 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - ABC No Rio, undated; 13169 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - Angel Orensanz Foundation, undated; 13168 (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - Angel's, undated; 13167 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - The Art Market, undated; 13166 (Box 18, Folder 118)
    - Atticus Books and Music, undated; 13165 (Box 18, Folder 119)
    - Audart, undated; 13164 (Box 18, Folder 120)
    - Back Fence, undated; 13163 (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - The Baggot Inn, undated; 13162 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Barnes and Noble, undated; 13161 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bellevue Art Museum, undated; 13160 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Biblio's, undated; 13159 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Bridge, undated; 13158 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn Museum of Art, undated; 13157 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - CBGB, undated; 13156 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - CUNY, undated; 13155 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Cafe Nico, undated; 13154 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Cafe Fuerte, undated; 13153 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Celeste Bartos Forum, undated; 13152 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Cendrillon, undated; 13151 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Ceres Gallery, undated; 13150 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - The Charleston, undated; 13149 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Civic Center Synagogue, undated; 13148 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Chez LaRoe, undated; 13147 (Box 1, Folder 23a.)
    - CLUB 86ed, undated; 13146 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Columbia University, undated; 13145 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Creation, undated; 13144 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Crystalina's, undated; 13143 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Dia Center for the Arts, undated; 13142 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - A Different Light, undated; 13141 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Dixon Place, undated; 13140 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Don's Hill, undated; 13139 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - The Drawing Center, undated; 13138 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - E3 Gallery, undated; 13137 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - The Ear Inn, undated; 13136 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Eidia House West, undated; 13135 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Fales Library, undated; 13134 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - The Farm, undated; 13133 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Gallery Stendhal, undated; 13132 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - The Gershwin Hotel, undated; 13131 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Globe Cafe, undated; 13130 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Granary Books, undated; 13129 (Box 1, Folder 40a.)
    - HERE, undated; 13128 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - IN-Flux, undated; 13127 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Jack Tilton Gallery, undated; 13126 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - KGB, undated; 13125 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Kinokuniya Bookstore, undated; 13124 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Knitting Factory, undated; 13123 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - La Mama La Galleria, undated; 13122 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - The Lamb's Theater, undated; 13121 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Le Gamin Chelsea, undated; 13120 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Life, undated; 13119 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - The Little Theater, undated; 13118 (Box 1, Folder 50a.)
    - Mare Chiaro, undated; 13117 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Marymount Manhattan College, undated; 13116 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Medicine Show Theater, undated; 13115 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Mendez Mural Garden, undated; 13114 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Middle Collegiate Church Women's Guild, undated; 13113 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - MIX, undated; 13112 (Box 1, Folder 55a.)
    - Mr. Babbington's, undated; 13111 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - The National Arts Club, undated; 13110 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - National Design Museum, undated; 13109 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - New School for Social Research, undated; 13108 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - The News Room, undated; 13107 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Opera, undated; 13106 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Pace Wildenstein, undated; 13105 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Phlebus Book Shop, undated; 13104 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - The Phoenix Gallery, undated; 13103 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - The Pink Pony, undated; 13102 (Box 1, Folder 64a.)
    - The Poetry Project, undated; 13101 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Poets and Writers, undated; 13100 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Poet's House, undated; 13099 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Poet's Theater, undated; 13098 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Printed Matter, Inc., undated; 13097 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Puerto Rican Traveling Theater, undated; 13096 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Queer Hall, undated; 13095 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Rising Cafe, undated; 13094 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Romanian Cultural Center, undated; 13093 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Roulette, undated; 13092 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Ruse, undated; 13091 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - The Salon, undated; 13090 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Savoy Lounge, undated; 13089 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Segue Foundation Performance Space, undated; 13088 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Serena, undated; 13087 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Siberia, undated; 13086 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Sixth and B Garden, undated; 13085 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Small Press Center, undated; 13084 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Sotheby's, undated; 13083 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Spacewurm, undated; 13082 (Box 1, Folder 83a.)
    - The Speakeasy Cafe, undated; 13081 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Starve Theater, undated; 13080 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Stefan Stux Gallery, undated; 13079 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Studio 17, undated; 13078 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Surf Reality's X-Tasy Salon, undated; 13077 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Tibor De Nagy Gallery, undated; 13076 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Tonic, undated; 13075 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Tower Books, undated; 13074 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Tribes Gallery, undated; 13073 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Tricia Collins: Grand Salon, undated; 13072 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Video Lounge, undated; 13071 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Void, undated; 13070 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - WNYE, undated; 13069 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Way of Action Studio, undated; 13068 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - West Chelsea Arts Building, undated; 13067 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - White Columns, undated; 13066 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Williamsburg Art and Historical Center, undated; 13065 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Zinc Bar, undated; 13064 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements, 13012
    - 304 art, undated; 13062 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Laurie, undated; 13061 (Box 1, Folder 1a.)
    - Andrucyk, Inez, undated; 13060 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Audart, undated; 13059 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Books & Co., undated; 13058 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cafe Brazil, undated; 13057 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cummings Arts Center, undated; 13056 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Duplex Cabaret, undated; 13054 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dursee, Brian J., undated; 13053 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Eighth Floor Gallery, undated; 13052 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Fotouhi Cramer Gallery, undated; 13051 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Galapagos Space, undated; 13050 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Gale Gates et al., undated; 13049 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Gracie Mansion Gallery, undated; 13048 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - HERE Arts Center, undated; 13047 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Himmelstein, Shelley, undated; 13046 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Iggy Pop, undated; 13044 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Joseph Hellman Gallery, undated; 13043 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - J Rainey Gallery, undated; 13042 (Box 1, Folder 17a.)
    - The Kitchen, undated; 13041 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Lance Fung Gallery, undated; 13040 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Malanga, Gerard, undated; 13039 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Mann, Frank, undated; 13038 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Martinez Gallery, undated; 13037 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Medicine Show, undated; 13036 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - NYU, undated; 13035 (Box 1, Folder 23a.)
    - Ochiishi, undated; 13034 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Orensanz Art Center, undated; 13033 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Pardo View, undated; 13032 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Pierogi 2000, 13031 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Pink Inc.'s So Grand Studio, undated; 13030 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Prospect Park Bandshell, undated; 13029 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Randall, Michael, undated; 13028 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Rene's Gallery, undated; 13027 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Roseland Ballroom, undated; 13026 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Siberia, undated; 13025 (Box 1, Folder 32a.)
    - Spectra Digital Arts Gallery, undated; 13024 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Streb/Ringside Studio, undated; 13023 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Subculture Gallery, undated; 13022 (Box 1, Folder 34a.)
    - Tompkins, Betty, undated; 13021 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Tribes Gallery, undated; 13020 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Tricia Collins Contemporary Art, undated; 13019 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Tunick, Spencer, undated; 13018 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Upstate Art, undated; 13017 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Verge, undated; 13016 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Winter, Patricia, undated; 13015 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated; 13014 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Yung, Susan, undated; 13013 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series VIII: Original Art, 13008
  - Shalom-"Millenium of Profitcy," 1999, 13010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stevenson, Patrick-7 Scary Planet Press Notecards, c1996: woodcarving print, handpainted, 13009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series IX: Ephemera, 13004
  Scope and Contents note
  Accretions 1995-1999 - Series IX box
  - Ephemera: Vinnie's Friggin' Magnet and Vinnie's Tampon Case, undated; 13006 (Box 19, Folder 150)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series XI: Posters, 13001
  - Cover the World poster w/art by Rodney Greenblatt, 1985, 13003 (Folder 12 Right)
  - Poetry in Motion series (sponsored by MTA, posted on MTA trains): Hal Sirowitz's "I Finally Managed to Speak to Her", undated; 13002 (Folder 11 Right)
  - Ben Katchor - The Jew of New York, 263527 (Folder 19)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series XII: Catalogs, 12976
  - Akashic Books, undated; 13000 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - Allied Productions, Inc., undated; 12999 (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - Autonomedia, undated; 12998 (Box 19, Folder 153)
  - Black Sparrow Press, undated; 12997 (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - Brookline Books, undated; 12996 (Box 19, Folder 155)
  - Edgewise Press, undated; 12995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Factsheet 5, undated; 12994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Four Walls Eight Windows, undated; 12993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Hanging Loose Press, undated; 12992 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Kaya, undated; 12991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Linear Arts Books, undated; 12990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Masquerade Books, undated; 12989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Mr. Puke Press, undated; 12988 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Roof Books, undated; 12987 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Seven Stories Press, undated; 12986 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Small Press Distribution, undated; 12985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Soft Skull Press, undated; 12984 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Spinsters Ink, undated; 12983 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Tangerine, undated; 12982 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - The Temple, undated; 12981 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Thin Air Video, undated; 12980 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Thundersmouth Press, undated; 12979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Undulating Bedsheets Productions, undated; 12978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Verso, undated; 12977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series XIV: Periodicals, 12932
  - American Book Review: Vol 14, No 6, Feb-Mar 1993. Vol 17, No 4, Apr-May 1996. Vol 17, No 5, Jun-Jul 1996. Vol 17, No 6, Aug-Sep 1996. Vol 18, No 1, Oct-Nov 1996. Vol 18, No 3, Mar-Apr 1997. Vol 18, No 2, Dec-Jan 1996-7., 1993-1997; 12975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Blueline: Note-repros inside of Larry Webb, Shelley Himmelstein, Bob Witz, undated; 12971 (Box 1, Folder 1d.)
  - Chakra: Fall 1990, 12969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chronogram: July 1999, 12968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cover: Vol 10, no 9, Holidays 1996-7, 12967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Creative Screenwriting: Vol 5, No 2, undated; 12966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Curse: Vol 3, No 1, undated; 12965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Eclectic: Vol 1, No 6, Aug 1999, 12963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fiction: Vol 14, No 1, undated; 12962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Home Planet News: No 41, 1997, 12960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ikon: Vol 1, No 1, Feb 1967; Vol 1, No 5, Mar 1968, 1967-1968; 12959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Juxtapoz:Vol 5, No 1, Spring 1998, 12957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Long Shot:Vol 22, 1999, 12956 (Box 1, Folder 11a.)
  - Lusty Mover: Premier Issue, Fall 1992-Huberman, "Stark Raving Sanity", 12955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Masquerade: Vol 6, No 6, Nov-Dec 1997, 12954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meat Epoch: No 16, 1993, 12953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Nexus: Vol 30, Fall 1994-Sparrow, "My Life in Prison," "A Ceremony," "Grapefruit," "Toilet", 12952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - New Observations: Issue No 123, Fall 1999, 12951 (Box 1, Folder 15a.)
  - Option: G2 Issue, Mar-Apr 1986; No 79, Mar-Apr 1998-Sonic Youth, 1986, 1998; 12949 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Out of Bounds: #2, Summer 1994, 12948 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Paper: April 1990, 12947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Paramour: Vol 2, Issue 4-Unbearables Fiction: Litzky, Maynard, Rutkowski, undated; 12946 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Poetry Calendar: Vol 21, No 6, Feb 1997. Vol 21, No 7, Mar 1997. Vol 24, No1, Sep 1999. Vol 24, No 2, Oct 1999. Vol 24, No 2, Oct 1999. Vol 24, No 3, Nov 1999., 1997-1999; 12945 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Poetry Project: Feb-Mar 1997, Issue #164; Apr-May 1997, Issue #165; Oct-Nov 1999, Issue #176, 1997-1999; 12944 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Public Illumination Magazine: No 46, Late 1999, 12943 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Rain Taxi: Vol 1, No 3, Summer 1996; Vol 1, No 4, Fall 1996; Vol 2, No1, N.d.; Vol 4, No 2, Summer 1999; Vol 4, No 3, Fall 1999., 12942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sandbox: No 4, Winter 96-97, 1996-1997; 12941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Sarasota Review of Poetry: Vol 3, 1999-Jenifer Nostrand, "The sky over Versailles," "The narrow back street," "'The Army of Angels'", 12940 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Stained Sheets: Late Summer-Early Fall 1999, Issue 23, 12939 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Sun: Issue 149, April 1988: Issue 181, Dec 1990: Issue 190, Sep 1991: Issue 194, N.d.: Issue 251, Nov 1996: Issue 257, May 1997., 1988-1997; 12938 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Up Front News: Jan 15, 1997; Dec 4, 1996, 1997, 1996; 12937 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Washington Free Press: No 41, Sep-Oct 1999, 12935 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Wetbones: No 2, Fall 1997-Rob Hardin, "Exterminating the Angels", 12934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Wordwrights!: No 9, Winter 1997-Mary Leary, "A Certain Blue," "Modern Religion", 12933 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series I: Correspondence, 262993
  - Kaufman, Alan, undated; 13565 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series III: The Unbearables, 262995
  - Subseries A: The Unbearables, 262996
    - New York Times Magazine article, 2/19/95, 262997 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Daily News Article, 3//5/95, 1995; 262998 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Poetry Videos Sale Sheet, Brooklyn Bridge 95-96, 1995-1996; 263001 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Poster-Poetry Project's Celebration of 3 Decades, May 1997, 263002 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - W articles, 96-97, 1996-1997; 263003 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Rent/Rant Stuff, 1998, 263011 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Crimes of the Beats, 262999
    - Life article-1957, 1959 (oversize), 263000 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Article re: Beats online, 1995, 263012 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Poster for film "Hey, Jack Kerouac," Dec 1995, 263013 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - 1996 Poetry Flash article re: Jack Kerouac, 263014 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - American Book Jam Special Issue, 8/97, 1997; 263015 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - City Magazine International (French) article, N.d., 263016 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - VLS article re Kerouac, Oct-Nov 1999, 263017 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series IV: Subject Files, 263010
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists, 263022
    - Alexander, Vikky, undated; 263023 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Benderson, Bruce, undated; 263026 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Charnick, A., undated; 263135 (Box 34, Folder 17Cooper, Dennis (oversize))
    - Cooper, Dennis, undated; 263136 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Delany, Samuel, undated; 263137 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Indiana, Gary, undated; 263138 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Katchor, Ben, undated; 263139 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Kuper, Peter, undated; 263140 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Plantenga, Bart, undated; 263141 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Sandlin, David, undated; 263142 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Sapphire, undated; 263143 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Sparrow, undated; 263144 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Ulin, David, undated; 263145 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Witz, Bob, undated; 263146 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated; 263151 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects, 263024
    - Between C & D, undated; 263025 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Soho scene, undated; 263152 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - General Subject Misc., undated; 263153 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series VI: Announcements, 263147
  - Subseries B: Gallery Show Announcements, 263148
    - Duplex, The, undated; 263149 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Hsieh, Tehching, undated; 263150 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Oversize - Series XIV: Periodicals, 263154
  - Appearances materials for Issue #26, undated; 263155 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Aquarian: Issue No 825, May 22-29, 1996. Issue No 827, June 5-12, 1996. Issue No 828, June 12-19, 1996. Issue No 859, Jan 15-22, 1997., 1996-1997; 12973 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Artforum: Sept 1973, 12972 (Box 35, Folder 3)